http://alpena18.secure.cusolutionsgroup.net/privacy

Privacy
Your privacy is our main concern! To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with state and federal laws including computer safeguards as well as secured files and buildings. We also restrict access to your personal information to only those employees who need to know to perform his/her job duties or to provide you with quality products and services.
Like all financial institutions, though, we do need to share some of your personal information as part of our everyday business. But, what does Alpena Alcona Area Credit Union do with your personal information? Let our privacy policy explain that to you…
Privacy Policy
To protect children’s privacy online, AAACU does not collect or retain any personal information on its website from children under the age of 13.
AAACU does, however, use small text files called cookies to collect anonymous website traffic data. This information helps improve our web services. Our cookies do not collect or store any personally identifiable information.
Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party sites linked within our web pages. For further information you should consult the privacy disclosures of the third party site(s).
Alpena Alcona Area Credit Union will never call, email or otherwise contact you and ask for your personal, confidential information. Contact us immediately if you ever suspect fraud or receive suspicious emails, text messages or phone calls about your credit union account.
And, remember, protect yourself! Do not send personal, confidential information such as your account number, PIN, credit card number or social security number through unsecure channels such as email. Instead, use our home banking product to send us secure information. If you cannot access our home banking site, call us, fax us or send us an email with your name and phone number only.
If you have any questions or comments regarding AAACU’s Privacy Policy Statement, please send us an e-mail at aaacu@aaacu.com or you may contact us at (989) 356-3577 or 1-800-443-3577. You may also write us at:
Alpena Alcona Area Credit Union
1100 S Bagley St.
PO Box 515
Alpena, MI 49707
